<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="style/moviecatalog.xsl"?>
<!DOCTYPE catalog SYSTEM "data/catalog.dtd">


<catalog>
	<movie>
		<id>0</id>
		<image>img/tt0119137.jpg</image>
		<score>5</score>
		<genre>Comedy</genre>
		<title>Flubber</title>
		<year>1997</year>
		<description>An absent-minded professor discovers &quot;flubber,&quot; a rubber-like super-bouncy substance.</description>
		<price>8</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>1</id>
		<image>img/tt0111161.jpg</image>
		<score>9.3</score>
		<genre>Crime</genre>
		<title>The Shawshank Redemption</title>
		<year>1994</year>
		<description>Two imprisoned men bond over a number of years, finding solace and eventual redemption through acts of common decency.</description>
		<price>1</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>2</id>
		<image>img/tt0068646.jpg</image>
		<score>9.2</score>
		<genre>Crime</genre>
		<title>The Godfather</title>
		<year>1972</year>
		<description>The aging patriarch of an organized crime dynasty transfers control of his clandestine empire to his reluctant son.</description>
		<price>1</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>3</id>
		<image>img/tt0071562.jpg</image>
		<score>9.1</score>
		<genre>Crime</genre>
		<title>The Godfather: Part II</title>
		<year>1974</year>
		<description>The early life and career of Vito Corleone in 1920s New York is portrayed while his son, Michael, expands and tightens his grip on his crime syndicate stretching from Lake Tahoe, Nevada to pre-revolution 1958 Cuba.</description>
		<price>7</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>4</id>
		<image>img/tt0468569.jpg</image>
		<score>9</score>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<title>The Dark Knight</title>
		<year>2008</year>
		<description>When the menace known as the Joker wreaks havoc and chaos on the people of Gotham, the caped crusader must come to terms with one of the greatest psychological tests of his ability to fight injustice.</description>
		<price>4</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>5</id>
		<image>img/tt0110912.jpg</image>
		<score>9</score>
		<genre>Crime</genre>
		<title>Pulp Fiction</title>
		<year>1994</year>
		<description>The lives of two mob hit men, a boxer, a gangster's wife, and a pair of diner bandits intertwine in four tales of violence and redemption.</description>
		<price>5</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>6</id>
		<image>img/tt0060196.jpg</image>
		<score>9</score>
		<genre>Western</genre>
		<title>The Good, the Bad and the Ugly</title>
		<year>1966</year>
		<description>A bounty hunting scam joins two men in an uneasy alliance against a third in a race to find a fortune in gold buried in a remote cemetery.</description>
		<price>7</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>7</id>
		<image>img/tt0108052.jpg</image>
		<score>8.9</score>
		<genre>Biography</genre>
		<title>Schindler's List</title>
		<year>1993</year>
		<description>In Poland during World War II, Oskar Schindler gradually becomes concerned for his Jewish workforce after witnessing their persecution by the Nazis.</description>
		<price>1</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>8</id>
		<image>img/tt0050083.jpg</image>
		<score>8.9</score>
		<genre>Drama</genre>
		<title>12 Angry Men</title>
		<year>1957</year>
		<description>A dissenting juror in a murder trial slowly manages to convince the others that the case is not as obviously clear as it seemed in court.</description>
		<price>4</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>9</id>
		<image>img/tt0167260.jpg</image>
		<score>8.9</score>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<title>The Lord of the Rings: The Return of the King</title>
		<year>2003</year>
		<description>Gandalf and Aragorn lead the World of Men against Sauron's army to draw his gaze from Frodo and Sam as they approach Mount Doom with the One Ring.</description>
		<price>5</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>10</id>
		<image>img/tt0137523.jpg</image>
		<score>8.9</score>
		<genre>Drama</genre>
		<title>Fight Club</title>
		<year>1999</year>
		<description>An insomniac office worker looking for a way to change his life crosses paths with a devil-may-care soap maker and they form an underground fight club that evolves into something much, much more...</description>
		<price>8</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>11</id>
		<image>img/tt0120737.jpg</image>
		<score>8.8</score>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<title>The Lord of the Rings: The Fellowship of the Ring</title>
		<year>2001</year>
		<description>A meek hobbit of the Shire and eight companions set out on a journey to Mount Doom to destroy the One Ring and the dark lord Sauron.</description>
		<price>3</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>12</id>
		<image>img/tt0080684.jpg</image>
		<score>8.8</score>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<title>Star Wars: Episode V - The Empire Strikes Back</title>
		<year>1980</year>
		<description>After the rebels have been brutally overpowered by the Empire on their newly established base, Luke Skywalker takes advanced Jedi training with Master Yoda, while his friends are pursued by Darth Vader as part of his plan to capture Luke.</description>
		<price>2</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>13</id>
		<image>img/tt1375666.jpg</image>
		<score>8.8</score>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<title>Inception</title>
		<year>2010</year>
		<description>A thief who steals corporate secrets through use of dream-sharing technology is given the inverse task of planting an idea into the mind of a CEO.</description>
		<price>4</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>14</id>
		<image>img/tt0109830.jpg</image>
		<score>8.8</score>
		<genre>Drama</genre>
		<title>Forrest Gump</title>
		<year>1994</year>
		<description>Forrest Gump, while not intelligent, has accidentally been present at many historic moments, but his true love, Jenny Curran, eludes him.</description>
		<price>8</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>15</id>
		<image>img/tt0073486.jpg</image>
		<score>8.8</score>
		<genre>Drama</genre>
		<title>One Flew Over the Cuckoo's Nest</title>
		<year>1975</year>
		<description>Upon admittance to a mental institution, a brash rebel rallies the patients to take on the oppressive head nurse.</description>
		<price>2</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>16</id>
		<image>img/tt0167261.jpg</image>
		<score>8.8</score>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<title>The Lord of the Rings: The Two Towers</title>
		<year>2002</year>
		<description>While Frodo and Sam edge closer to Mordor with the help of the shifty Gollum, the divided fellowship makes a stand against Sauron's new ally, Saruman, and his hordes of Isengard.</description>
		<price>7</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>17</id>
		<image>img/tt0099685.jpg</image>
		<score>8.7</score>
		<genre>Biography</genre>
		<title>Goodfellas</title>
		<year>1990</year>
		<description>Henry Hill and his friends work their way up through the mob hierarchy.</description>
		<price>3</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>18</id>
		<image>img/tt0133093.jpg</image>
		<score>8.7</score>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<title>The Matrix</title>
		<year>1999</year>
		<description>A computer hacker learns from mysterious rebels about the true nature of his reality and his role in the war against its controllers.</description>
		<price>1</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>19</id>
		<image>img/tt0076759.jpg</image>
		<score>8.7</score>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<title>Star Wars</title>
		<year>1977</year>
		<description>Luke Skywalker joins forces with a Jedi Knight, a cocky pilot, a wookiee and two droids to save the universe from the Empire's world-destroying battle-station, while also attempting to rescue Princess Leia from the evil Darth Vader.</description>
		<price>7</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>20</id>
		<image>img/tt0047478.jpg</image>
		<score>8.7</score>
		<genre>Drama</genre>
		<title>Seven Samurai</title>
		<year>1954</year>
		<description>A poor village under attack by bandits recruits seven unemployed samurai to help them defend themselves.</description>
		<price>6</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>21</id>
		<image>img/tt0317248.jpg</image>
		<score>8.7</score>
		<genre>Crime</genre>
		<title>City of God</title>
		<year>2002</year>
		<description>Two boys growing up in a violent neighborhood of Rio de Janeiro take different paths: one becomes a photographer, the other a drug dealer.</description>
		<price>5</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>22</id>
		<image>img/tt0114369.jpg</image>
		<score>8.7</score>
		<genre>Drama</genre>
		<title>Se7en</title>
		<year>1995</year>
		<description>Two detectives, a rookie and a veteran, hunt a serial killer who uses the seven deadly sins as his modus operandi.</description>
		<price>6</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>23</id>
		<image>img/tt0114814.jpg</image>
		<score>8.7</score>
		<genre>Crime</genre>
		<title>The Usual Suspects</title>
		<year>1995</year>
		<description>A sole survivor tells of the twisty events leading up to a horrific gun battle on a boat, which begin when five criminals meet at a seemingly random police lineup.</description>
		<price>0</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>24</id>
		<image>img/tt0102926.jpg</image>
		<score>8.6</score>
		<genre>Crime</genre>
		<title>The Silence of the Lambs</title>
		<year>1991</year>
		<description>A young F.B.I. cadet must confide in an incarcerated and manipulative killer to receive his help on catching another serial killer who skins his victims.</description>
		<price>6</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>25</id>
		<image>img/tt0038650.jpg</image>
		<score>8.7</score>
		<genre>Drama</genre>
		<title>It's a Wonderful Life</title>
		<year>1946</year>
		<description>An angel helps a compassionate but despairingly frustrated businessman by showing what life would have been like if he never existed.</description>
		<price>5</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>26</id>
		<image>img/tt0064116.jpg</image>
		<score>8.7</score>
		<genre>Western</genre>
		<title>Once Upon a Time in the West</title>
		<year>1968</year>
		<description>Epic story of a mysterious stranger with a harmonica who joins forces with a notorious desperado to protect a beautiful widow from a ruthless assassin working for the railroad.</description>
		<price>3</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>27</id>
		<image>img/tt0110413.jpg</image>
		<score>8.6</score>
		<genre>Crime</genre>
		<title>Léon: The Professional</title>
		<year>1994</year>
		<description>A professional assassin rescues a young girl whose family were killed in a police raid.</description>
		<price>4</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>28</id>
		<image>img/tt0118799.jpg</image>
		<score>8.6</score>
		<genre>Comedy</genre>
		<title>Life Is Beautiful</title>
		<year>1997</year>
		<description>A Jewish man has a wonderful romance with the help of his humour, but must use that same quality to protect his son in a Nazi death camp.</description>
		<price>1</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>29</id>
		<image>img/tt0034583.jpg</image>
		<score>8.6</score>
		<genre>Drama</genre>
		<title>Casablanca</title>
		<year>1942</year>
		<description>Set in unoccupied Africa during the early days of World War II: An American expatriate meets a former lover, with unforeseen complications.</description>
		<price>3</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>30</id>
		<image>img/tt0082971.jpg</image>
		<score>8.6</score>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<title>Raiders of the Lost Ark</title>
		<year>1981</year>
		<description>Archeologist and adventurer Indiana Jones is hired by the US government to find the Ark of the Covenant before the Nazis.</description>
		<price>6</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>31</id>
		<image>img/tt0120586.jpg</image>
		<score>8.6</score>
		<genre>Crime</genre>
		<title>American History X</title>
		<year>1998</year>
		<description>A former neo-nazi skinhead tries to prevent his younger brother from going down the same wrong path that he did.</description>
		<price>0</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>32</id>
		<image>img/tt0054215.jpg</image>
		<score>8.6</score>
		<genre>Horror</genre>
		<title>Psycho</title>
		<year>1960</year>
		<description>A Phoenix secretary steals $40,000 from her employer's client, goes on the run and checks into a remote motel run by a young man under the domination of his mother.</description>
		<price>8</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>33</id>
		<image>img/tt0120815.jpg</image>
		<score>8.6</score>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<title>Saving Private Ryan</title>
		<year>1998</year>
		<description>Following the Normandy Landings, a group of U.S. soldiers go behind enemy lines to retrieve a paratrooper whose brothers have been killed in action.</description>
		<price>3</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>34</id>
		<image>img/tt0047396.jpg</image>
		<score>8.6</score>
		<genre>Mystery</genre>
		<title>Rear Window</title>
		<year>1954</year>
		<description>A wheelchair bound photographer spies on his neighbours from his apartment window and becomes convinced one of them has committed murder.</description>
		<price>2</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>35</id>
		<image>img/tt0021749.jpg</image>
		<score>8.6</score>
		<genre>Comedy</genre>
		<title>City Lights</title>
		<year>1931</year>
		<description>The Tramp struggles to help a blind flower girl he has fallen in love with.</description>
		<price>2</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>36</id>
		<image>img/tt0245429.jpg</image>
		<score>8.6</score>
		<genre>Animation</genre>
		<title>Spirited Away</title>
		<year>2001</year>
		<description>In the middle of her family's move to the suburbs, a sullen 10-year-old girl wanders into a world ruled by gods, witches, and monsters; where humans are changed into animals; and a bathhouse for these creatures.</description>
		<price>2</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>37</id>
		<image>img/tt1675434.jpg</image>
		<score>8.6</score>
		<genre>Biography</genre>
		<title>The Intouchables</title>
		<year>2011</year>
		<description>After he becomes a quadriplegic from a paragliding accident, an aristocrat hires a young man from the projects to be his caretaker.</description>
		<price>5</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>38</id>
		<image>img/tt0027977.jpg</image>
		<score>8.6</score>
		<genre>Comedy</genre>
		<title>Modern Times</title>
		<year>1936</year>
		<description>The Tramp struggles to live in modern industrial society with the help of a young homeless woman.</description>
		<price>3</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>39</id>
		<image>img/tt0103064.jpg</image>
		<score>8.5</score>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<title>Terminator 2: Judgment Day</title>
		<year>1991</year>
		<description>A cyborg, identical to the one who failed to kill Sarah Connor, must now protect her ten-year-old son, John, from a more advanced cyborg, made out of liquid metal.</description>
		<price>2</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>40</id>
		<image>img/tt0209144.jpg</image>
		<score>8.5</score>
		<genre>Mystery</genre>
		<title>Memento</title>
		<year>2000</year>
		<description>A man, suffering from short-term memory loss, uses notes and tattoos to hunt for the man he thinks killed his wife.</description>
		<price>7</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>41</id>
		<image>img/tt0253474.jpg</image>
		<score>8.5</score>
		<genre>Biography</genre>
		<title>The Pianist</title>
		<year>2002</year>
		<description>A Polish Jewish musician struggles to survive the destruction of the Warsaw ghetto of World War II.</description>
		<price>3</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>42</id>
		<image>img/tt0120689.jpg</image>
		<score>8.5</score>
		<genre>Crime</genre>
		<title>The Green Mile</title>
		<year>1999</year>
		<description>The lives of guards on Death Row are affected by one of their charges: a black man accused of child murder and rape, yet who has a mysterious gift.</description>
		<price>6</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>43</id>
		<image>img/tt0043014.jpg</image>
		<score>8.6</score>
		<genre>Drama</genre>
		<title>Sunset Blvd.</title>
		<year>1950</year>
		<description>A hack screenwriter writes a screenplay for a former silent-film star who has faded into Hollywood obscurity.</description>
		<price>7</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>44</id>
		<image>img/tt0078788.jpg</image>
		<score>8.5</score>
		<genre>Drama</genre>
		<title>Apocalypse Now</title>
		<year>1979</year>
		<description>During the Vietnam War, Captain Willard is sent on a dangerous mission into Cambodia to assassinate a renegade colonel who has set himself up as a god among a local tribe.</description>
		<price>6</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>45</id>
		<image>img/tt0057012.jpg</image>
		<score>8.5</score>
		<genre>Comedy</genre>
		<title>Dr. Strangelove or: How I Learned to Stop Worrying and Love the Bomb</title>
		<year>1964</year>
		<description>An insane general triggers a path to nuclear holocaust that a war room full of politicians and generals frantically try to stop.</description>
		<price>0</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>46</id>
		<image>img/tt0407887.jpg</image>
		<score>8.5</score>
		<genre>Crime</genre>
		<title>The Departed</title>
		<year>2006</year>
		<description>An undercover state cop who has infiltrated an Irish gang and a mole in the police force working for the same mob race to track down and identify each other before being exposed to the enemy, after both sides realize their outfit has a rat.</description>
		<price>2</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>47</id>
		<image>img/tt0172495.jpg</image>
		<score>8.5</score>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<title>Gladiator</title>
		<year>2000</year>
		<description>When a Roman general is betrayed and his family murdered by an emperor's corrupt son, he comes to Rome as a gladiator to seek revenge.</description>
		<price>3</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>48</id>
		<image>img/tt0088763.jpg</image>
		<score>8.5</score>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<title>Back to the Future</title>
		<year>1985</year>
		<description>A young man is accidentally sent 30 years into the past in a time-traveling DeLorean invented by his friend, Dr. Emmett Brown, and must make sure his high-school-age parents unite in order to save his own existence.</description>
		<price>0</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>49</id>
		<image>img/tt0078748.jpg</image>
		<score>8.5</score>
		<genre>Horror</genre>
		<title>Alien</title>
		<year>1979</year>
		<description>The commercial vessel Nostromo receives a distress call from an unexplored planet. After searching for survivors, the crew heads home only to realize that a deadly bioform has joined them.</description>
		<price>4</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>50</id>
		<image>img/tt1065073.jpg</image>
		<score>8.7</score>
		<genre>Drama</genre>
		<title>Boyhood</title>
		<year>2014</year>
		<description>The life of a young man, Mason, from age 5 to age 18.</description>
		<price>7</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>51</id>
		<image>img/tt0482571.jpg</image>
		<score>8.5</score>
		<genre>Drama</genre>
		<title>The Prestige</title>
		<year>2006</year>
		<description>The rivalry between two magicians becomes more exacerbated by their attempt to perform the ultimate illusion.</description>
		<price>3</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>52</id>
		<image>img/tt1345836.jpg</image>
		<score>8.6</score>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<title>The Dark Knight Rises</title>
		<year>2012</year>
		<description>A new menace emerges and the Dark Knight rises again to protect the city from a merciless terrorist with the help of anti-heroine Selina Kyle.</description>
		<price>4</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>53</id>
		<image>img/tt0405094.jpg</image>
		<score>8.5</score>
		<genre>Drama</genre>
		<title>The Lives of Others</title>
		<year>2006</year>
		<description>In 1984 East Berlin, an agent of the secret police, conducting surveillance on a writer and his lover, finds himself becoming increasingly absorbed by their lives.</description>
		<price>7</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>54</id>
		<image>img/tt1853728.jpg</image>
		<score>8.5</score>
		<genre>Western</genre>
		<title>Django Unchained</title>
		<year>2012</year>
		<description>With the help of a German bounty hunter, a freed slave sets out to rescue his wife from a brutal Mississippi plantation owner.</description>
		<price>5</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>55</id>
		<image>img/tt0032553.jpg</image>
		<score>8.5</score>
		<genre>Comedy</genre>
		<title>The Great Dictator</title>
		<year>1940</year>
		<description>Dictator Adenoid Hynkel tries to expand his empire while a poor Jewish barber tries to avoid persecution from Hynkel's regime.</description>
		<price>1</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>56</id>
		<image>img/tt0110357.jpg</image>
		<score>8.5</score>
		<genre>Animation</genre>
		<title>The Lion King</title>
		<year>1994</year>
		<description>Tricked into thinking that he caused the death of his own father, a young lion cub flees and abandons his destiny as the future king.</description>
		<price>3</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>57</id>
		<image>img/tt0081505.jpg</image>
		<score>8.5</score>
		<genre>Horror</genre>
		<title>The Shining</title>
		<year>1980</year>
		<description>A family heads to an isolated hotel for the winter where an evil and spiritual presence influences the father into violence, while his psychic son sees horrific forebodings from the past and of the future.</description>
		<price>1</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>58</id>
		<image>img/tt0095765.jpg</image>
		<score>8.5</score>
		<genre>Drama</genre>
		<title>Cinema Paradiso</title>
		<year>1988</year>
		<description>A filmmaker recalls his childhood, when he fell in love with the movies at his village's theater and formed a deep friendship with the theater's projectionist.</description>
		<price>8</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>59</id>
		<image>img/tt0050825.jpg</image>
		<score>8.5</score>
		<genre>Drama</genre>
		<title>Paths of Glory</title>
		<year>1957</year>
		<description>When soldiers in World War I refuse to continue with an impossible attack, their superior officers decide to make an example of them.</description>
		<price>7</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>60</id>
		<image>img/tt0169547.jpg</image>
		<score>8.5</score>
		<genre>Drama</genre>
		<title>American Beauty</title>
		<year>1999</year>
		<description>A sexually frustrated suburban father has a mid-life crisis after becoming infatuated with his daughter's best friend.</description>
		<price>6</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>61</id>
		<image>img/tt0910970.jpg</image>
		<score>8.5</score>
		<genre>Animation</genre>
		<title>WALL·E</title>
		<year>2008</year>
		<description>In the distant future, a small waste collecting robot inadvertently embarks on a space journey that will ultimately decide the fate of mankind.</description>
		<price>8</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>62</id>
		<image>img/tt2015381.jpg</image>
		<score>8.5</score>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<title>Guardians of the Galaxy</title>
		<year>2014</year>
		<description>A group of space criminals must work together to stop the fanatical villain Ronan the Accuser from destroying the galaxy.</description>
		<price>7</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>63</id>
		<image>img/tt0053125.jpg</image>
		<score>8.5</score>
		<genre>Mystery</genre>
		<title>North by Northwest</title>
		<year>1959</year>
		<description>A hapless New York advertising executive is mistaken for a government agent by a group of foreign spies, and is pursued across the country while he looks for a way to survive.</description>
		<price>5</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>64</id>
		<image>img/tt0090605.jpg</image>
		<score>8.4</score>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<title>Aliens</title>
		<year>1986</year>
		<description>The planet from &quot;Alien&quot; has been colonized, but contact is lost. This time, the rescue team has impressive firepower, but will it be enough?</description>
		<price>1</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>65</id>
		<image>img/tt0033467.jpg</image>
		<score>8.4</score>
		<genre>Drama</genre>
		<title>Citizen Kane</title>
		<year>1941</year>
		<description>Following the death of a publishing tycoon, news reporters scramble to discover the meaning of his final utterance.</description>
		<price>3</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>66</id>
		<image>img/tt0211915.jpg</image>
		<score>8.5</score>
		<genre>Comedy</genre>
		<title>Amélie</title>
		<year>2001</year>
		<description>Amelie, an innocent and naive girl in Paris, with her own sense of justice, decides to help those around her and along the way, discovers love.</description>
		<price>5</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>67</id>
		<image>img/tt0052357.jpg</image>
		<score>8.4</score>
		<genre>Mystery</genre>
		<title>Vertigo</title>
		<year>1958</year>
		<description>A retired San Francisco detective suffering from acrophobia investigates the strange activities of an old friend's wife, all the while becoming dangerously obsessed with her.</description>
		<price>7</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>68</id>
		<image>img/tt0435761.jpg</image>
		<score>8.4</score>
		<genre>Animation</genre>
		<title>Toy Story 3</title>
		<year>2010</year>
		<description>The toys are mistakenly delivered to a day-care center instead of the attic right before Andy leaves for college, and it's up to Woody to convince the other toys that they weren't abandoned and to return home.</description>
		<price>5</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>69</id>
		<image>img/tt0022100.jpg</image>
		<score>8.5</score>
		<genre>Crime</genre>
		<title>M</title>
		<year>1931</year>
		<description>When the police in a German city are unable to catch a child-murderer, other criminals join in the manhunt.</description>
		<price>6</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>70</id>
		<image>img/tt0082096.jpg</image>
		<score>8.5</score>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<title>Das Boot</title>
		<year>1981</year>
		<description>The claustrophobic world of a WWII German U-boat; boredom, filth, and sheer terror.</description>
		<price>0</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>71</id>
		<image>img/tt0364569.jpg</image>
		<score>8.4</score>
		<genre>Drama</genre>
		<title>Oldboy</title>
		<year>2003</year>
		<description>After being kidnapped and imprisoned for 15 years, Oh Dae-Su is released, only to find that he must find his captor in 5 days.</description>
		<price>7</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>72</id>
		<image>img/tt0119698.jpg</image>
		<score>8.4</score>
		<genre>Animation</genre>
		<title>Princess Mononoke</title>
		<year>1997</year>
		<description>On a journey to find the cure for a Tatarigami's curse, Ashitaka finds himself in the middle of a war between the forest gods and Tatara, a mining colony. In this quest he also meets San, the Mononoke Hime.</description>
		<price>5</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>73</id>
		<image>img/tt0066921.jpg</image>
		<score>8.4</score>
		<genre>Crime</genre>
		<title>A Clockwork Orange</title>
		<year>1971</year>
		<description>In future Britain, charismatic delinquent Alex DeLarge is jailed and volunteers for an experimental aversion therapy developed by the government in an effort to solve society's crime problem - but not all goes according to plan.</description>
		<price>5</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>74</id>
		<image>img/tt0086190.jpg</image>
		<score>8.4</score>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<title>Star Wars: Episode VI - The Return of the Jedi</title>
		<year>1983</year>
		<description>After rescuing Han Solo from the palace of Jabba the Hutt, the rebels attempt to destroy the second Death Star, while Luke struggles to make Vader shake off of the dark side of the Force.</description>
		<price>7</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>75</id>
		<image>img/tt0095327.jpg</image>
		<score>8.5</score>
		<genre>Animation</genre>
		<title>Grave of the Fireflies</title>
		<year>1988</year>
		<description>A tragic film covering a young boy and his little sister's struggle to survive in Japan during World War II.</description>
		<price>4</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>76</id>
		<image>img/tt0075314.jpg</image>
		<score>8.4</score>
		<genre>Crime</genre>
		<title>Taxi Driver</title>
		<year>1976</year>
		<description>A mentally unstable Vietnam war veteran works as a night-time taxi driver in New York City where the perceived decadence and sleaze feeds his urge for violent action, attempting to save a preadolescent prostitute in the process.</description>
		<price>3</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>77</id>
		<image>img/tt0087843.jpg</image>
		<score>8.4</score>
		<genre>Crime</genre>
		<title>Once Upon a Time in America</title>
		<year>1984</year>
		<description>A former Prohibition-era Jewish gangster returns to the Lower East Side of Manhattan over thirty years later, where he once again must confront the ghosts and regrets of his old life.</description>
		<price>3</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>78</id>
		<image>img/tt0105236.jpg</image>
		<score>8.4</score>
		<genre>Crime</genre>
		<title>Reservoir Dogs</title>
		<year>1992</year>
		<description>After a simple jewelery heist goes terribly wrong, the surviving criminals begin to suspect that one of them is a police informant.</description>
		<price>8</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>79</id>
		<image>img/tt0036775.jpg</image>
		<score>8.4</score>
		<genre>Crime</genre>
		<title>Double Indemnity</title>
		<year>1944</year>
		<description>An insurance rep lets himself be talked into a murder/insurance fraud scheme that arouses an insurance investigator's suspicions.</description>
		<price>5</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>80</id>
		<image>img/tt2267998.jpg</image>
		<score>8.5</score>
		<genre>Drama</genre>
		<title>Gone Girl</title>
		<year>2014</year>
		<description>With his wife's disappearance having become the focus of an intense media circus, a man sees the spotlight turned on him when it's suspected that he may not be innocent.</description>
		<price>6</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>81</id>
		<image>img/tt0180093.jpg</image>
		<score>8.4</score>
		<genre>Drama</genre>
		<title>Requiem for a Dream</title>
		<year>2000</year>
		<description>The drug-induced utopias of four Coney Island people are shattered when their addictions become stronger.</description>
		<price>0</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>82</id>
		<image>img/tt0112573.jpg</image>
		<score>8.4</score>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<title>Braveheart</title>
		<year>1995</year>
		<description>When his secret bride is executed for assaulting an English soldier who tried to rape her, William Wallce begins a revolt and leads Scottish warriors against the cruel English tyrant who rules Scotland with an iron fist.</description>
		<price>8</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>83</id>
		<image>img/tt0056592.jpg</image>
		<score>8.4</score>
		<genre>Drama</genre>
		<title>To Kill a Mockingbird</title>
		<year>1962</year>
		<description>Atticus Finch, a lawyer in the Depression-era South, defends a black man against an undeserved rape charge, and his kids against prejudice.</description>
		<price>5</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>84</id>
		<image>img/tt0056172.jpg</image>
		<score>8.4</score>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<title>Lawrence of Arabia</title>
		<year>1962</year>
		<description>A flamboyant and controversial British military figure and his conflicted loyalties during his World War I service in the Middle East.</description>
		<price>8</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>85</id>
		<image>img/tt0338013.jpg</image>
		<score>8.4</score>
		<genre>Drama</genre>
		<title>Eternal Sunshine of the Spotless Mind</title>
		<year>2004</year>
		<description>A couple undergo a procedure to erase each other from their memories when their relationship turns sour, but it is only through the process of loss that they discover what they had to begin with.</description>
		<price>6</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>86</id>
		<image>img/tt0051201.jpg</image>
		<score>8.5</score>
		<genre>Crime</genre>
		<title>Witness for the Prosecution</title>
		<year>1957</year>
		<description>Leonard Vole is arrested on suspicion of murdering an elderly acquaintance. He employs an experienced but aging barrister as his defense attorney.</description>
		<price>4</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>87</id>
		<image>img/tt0093058.jpg</image>
		<score>8.4</score>
		<genre>Drama</genre>
		<title>Full Metal Jacket</title>
		<year>1987</year>
		<description>A pragmatic U.S. Marine observes the dehumanizing effects the U.S.-Vietnam War has on his fellow recruits from their brutal boot camp training to the bloody street fighting in Hue.</description>
		<price>3</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>88</id>
		<image>img/tt0045152.jpg</image>
		<score>8.4</score>
		<genre>Comedy</genre>
		<title>Singin' in the Rain</title>
		<year>1952</year>
		<description>A silent film production company and cast make a difficult transition to sound.</description>
		<price>6</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>89</id>
		<image>img/tt0070735.jpg</image>
		<score>8.4</score>
		<genre>Comedy</genre>
		<title>The Sting</title>
		<year>1973</year>
		<description>In 1930s Chicago, a young con man seeking revenge for his murdered partner teams up with a master of the big con to win a fortune from a criminal banker.</description>
		<price>8</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>90</id>
		<image>img/tt0040522.jpg</image>
		<score>8.4</score>
		<genre>Drama</genre>
		<title>Bicycle Thieves</title>
		<year>1948</year>
		<description>A man and his son search for a stolen bicycle vital for his job.</description>
		<price>7</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>91</id>
		<image>img/tt0086879.jpg</image>
		<score>8.4</score>
		<genre>Biography</genre>
		<title>Amadeus</title>
		<year>1984</year>
		<description>The incredible story of Wolfgang Amadeus Mozart, told by his peer and secret rival Antonio Salieri - now confined to an insane asylum.</description>
		<price>4</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>92</id>
		<image>img/tt0071853.jpg</image>
		<score>8.4</score>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<title>Monty Python and the Holy Grail</title>
		<year>1975</year>
		<description>King Arthur and his knights embark on a low-budget search for the Grail, encountering many very silly obstacles.</description>
		<price>6</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>93</id>
		<image>img/tt0208092.jpg</image>
		<score>8.3</score>
		<genre>Comedy</genre>
		<title>Snatch.</title>
		<year>2000</year>
		<description>Unscrupulous boxing promoters, violent bookmakers, a Russian gangster, incompetent amateur robbers, and supposedly Jewish jewelers fight to track down a priceless stolen diamond.</description>
		<price>6</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>94</id>
		<image>img/tt0119488.jpg</image>
		<score>8.3</score>
		<genre>Crime</genre>
		<title>L.A. Confidential</title>
		<year>1997</year>
		<description>As corruption grows in 1950s LA, three policemen - one strait-laced, one brutal, and one sleazy - investigate a series of murders with their own brand of justice.</description>
		<price>4</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>95</id>
		<image>img/tt0042192.jpg</image>
		<score>8.4</score>
		<genre>Drama</genre>
		<title>All About Eve</title>
		<year>1950</year>
		<description>An ingenue insinuates herself in to the company of an established but aging stage actress and her circle of theater friends.</description>
		<price>6</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>96</id>
		<image>img/tt0042876.jpg</image>
		<score>8.4</score>
		<genre>Crime</genre>
		<title>Rashômon</title>
		<year>1950</year>
		<description>A heinous crime and its aftermath are recalled from differing points of view.</description>
		<price>4</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>97</id>
		<image>img/tt0053604.jpg</image>
		<score>8.4</score>
		<genre>Comedy</genre>
		<title>The Apartment</title>
		<year>1960</year>
		<description>A man tries to rise in his company by letting its executives use his apartment for trysts, but complications and a romance of his own ensue.</description>
		<price>8</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>98</id>
		<image>img/tt0059578.jpg</image>
		<score>8.3</score>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<title>For a Few Dollars More</title>
		<year>1965</year>
		<description>Two bounty hunters with the same intentions, team up to track down a Western outlaw.</description>
		<price>5</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>99</id>
		<image>img/tt0040897.jpg</image>
		<score>8.4</score>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<title>The Treasure of the Sierra Madre</title>
		<year>1948</year>
		<description>Fred Dobbs and Bob Curtin, two Americans searching for work in Mexico, convince an old prospector to help them mine for gold in the Sierra Madre Mountains.</description>
		<price>0</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>100</id>
		<image>img/tt0053291.jpg</image>
		<score>8.3</score>
		<genre>Comedy</genre>
		<title>Some Like It Hot</title>
		<year>1959</year>
		<description>When two musicians witness a mob hit, they flee the state in an all female band disguised as women, but further complications set in.</description>
		<price>8</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>101</id>
		<image>img/tt0012349.jpg</image>
		<score>8.4</score>
		<genre>Comedy</genre>
		<title>The Kid</title>
		<year>1921</year>
		<description>The Tramp cares for an abandoned child, but events put that relationship in jeopardy.</description>
		<price>4</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>102</id>
		<image>img/tt0041959.jpg</image>
		<score>8.4</score>
		<genre>Film-Noir</genre>
		<title>The Third Man</title>
		<year>1949</year>
		<description>Pulp novelist Holly Martins travels to shadowy, postwar Vienna, only to find himself investigating the mysterious death of an old friend, black-market opportunist Harry Lime.</description>
		<price>8</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>103</id>
		<image>img/tt0361748.jpg</image>
		<score>8.3</score>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<title>Inglourious Basterds</title>
		<year>2009</year>
		<description>In Nazi-occupied France during World War II, a plan to assassinate Nazi leaders by a group of Jewish U.S. soldiers coincides with a theatre owner's vengeful plans for the same.</description>
		<price>2</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>104</id>
		<image>img/tt0097576.jpg</image>
		<score>8.3</score>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<title>Indiana Jones and the Last Crusade</title>
		<year>1989</year>
		<description>When Dr. Henry Jones Sr. suddenly goes missing while pursuing the Holy Grail, eminent archaeologist Indiana Jones must follow in his father's footsteps and stop the Nazis.</description>
		<price>6</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>105</id>
		<image>img/tt0062622.jpg</image>
		<score>8.3</score>
		<genre>Mystery</genre>
		<title>2001: A Space Odyssey</title>
		<year>1968</year>
		<description>Humanity finds a mysterious, obviously artificial, object buried beneath the Lunar surface and, with the intelligent computer H.A.L. 9000, sets off on a quest.</description>
		<price>2</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>106</id>
		<image>img/tt1832382.jpg</image>
		<score>8.5</score>
		<genre>Drama</genre>
		<title>A Separation</title>
		<year>2011</year>
		<description>A married couple are faced with a difficult decision - to improve the life of their child by moving to another country or to stay in Iran and look after a deteriorating parent who has Alzheimer's disease.</description>
		<price>1</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>107</id>
		<image>img/tt0372784.jpg</image>
		<score>8.3</score>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<title>Batman Begins</title>
		<year>2005</year>
		<description>After training with his mentor, Batman begins his war on crime to free the crime-ridden Gotham City from corruption that the Scarecrow and the League of Shadows have cast upon it.</description>
		<price>8</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>108</id>
		<image>img/tt0055630.jpg</image>
		<score>8.4</score>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<title>Yojimbo</title>
		<year>1961</year>
		<description>A crafty ronin comes to a town divided by two criminal gangs and decides to play them against each other to free the town.</description>
		<price>4</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>109</id>
		<image>img/tt0017136.jpg</image>
		<score>8.3</score>
		<genre>Drama</genre>
		<title>Metropolis</title>
		<year>1927</year>
		<description>In a futuristic city sharply divided between the working class and the city planners, the son of the city's mastermind falls in love with a working class prophet who predicts the coming of a savior to mediate their differences.</description>
		<price>3</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>110</id>
		<image>img/tt0114709.jpg</image>
		<score>8.3</score>
		<genre>Animation</genre>
		<title>Toy Story</title>
		<year>1995</year>
		<description>A cowboy doll is profoundly threatened and jealous when a new spaceman figure supplants him as top toy in a boy's room.</description>
		<price>8</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>111</id>
		<image>img/tt0105695.jpg</image>
		<score>8.3</score>
		<genre>Western</genre>
		<title>Unforgiven</title>
		<year>1992</year>
		<description>Retired Old West gunslinger William Munny reluctantly takes on one last job, with the help of his old partner and a young man.</description>
		<price>2</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>112</id>
		<image>img/tt0081398.jpg</image>
		<score>8.3</score>
		<genre>Biography</genre>
		<title>Raging Bull</title>
		<year>1980</year>
		<description>An emotionally self-destructive boxer's journey through life, as the violence and temper that leads him to the top in the ring, destroys his life outside it.</description>
		<price>2</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>113</id>
		<image>img/tt0086250.jpg</image>
		<score>8.3</score>
		<genre>Crime</genre>
		<title>Scarface</title>
		<year>1983</year>
		<description>In 1980 Miami, a determined Cuban immigrant takes over a drug cartel while succumbing to greed.</description>
		<price>6</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>114</id>
		<image>img/tt0071315.jpg</image>
		<score>8.3</score>
		<genre>Drama</genre>
		<title>Chinatown</title>
		<year>1974</year>
		<description>A private detective hired to expose an adulterer finds himself caught up in a web of deceit, corruption and murder.</description>
		<price>4</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>115</id>
		<image>img/tt1049413.jpg</image>
		<score>8.3</score>
		<genre>Animation</genre>
		<title>Up</title>
		<year>2009</year>
		<description>To avoid being taken away to a nursing home, an old widower tries to fly his home to Paradise Falls, South America, along with a boy scout who accidently lifted off with him.</description>
		<price>1</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>116</id>
		<image>img/tt0095016.jpg</image>
		<score>8.3</score>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<title>Die Hard</title>
		<year>1988</year>
		<description>John McClane, officer of the NYPD, tries to save wife Holly Gennaro and several others, taken hostage by German terrorist Hans Gruber during a Christmas party at the Nakatomi Plaza in Los Angeles.</description>
		<price>8</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>117</id>
		<image>img/tt0363163.jpg</image>
		<score>8.3</score>
		<genre>Biography</genre>
		<title>Downfall</title>
		<year>2004</year>
		<description>Traudl Junge, the final secretary for Adolf Hitler, tells of the Nazi dictator's final days in his Berlin bunker at the end of WWII.</description>
		<price>0</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>118</id>
		<image>img/tt0986264.jpg</image>
		<score>8.5</score>
		<genre>Drama</genre>
		<title>Like Stars on Earth</title>
		<year>2007</year>
		<description>An eight year old boy is thought to be lazy and a troublemaker, until the new art teacher has the patience and compassion to discover the real problem behind his struggles in school.</description>
		<price>5</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>119</id>
		<image>img/tt0057115.jpg</image>
		<score>8.3</score>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<title>The Great Escape</title>
		<year>1963</year>
		<description>Allied P.O.W.s plan for several hundred of their number to escape from a German camp during World War II.</description>
		<price>6</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>120</id>
		<image>img/tt0457430.jpg</image>
		<score>8.3</score>
		<genre>Drama</genre>
		<title>Pan's Labyrinth</title>
		<year>2006</year>
		<description>In the falangist Spain of 1944, the bookish young stepdaughter of a sadistic army officer escapes into an eerie but captivating fantasy world.</description>
		<price>8</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>121</id>
		<image>img/tt0031679.jpg</image>
		<score>8.3</score>
		<genre>Drama</genre>
		<title>Mr. Smith Goes to Washington</title>
		<year>1939</year>
		<description>A naive man is appointed to fill a vacancy in the US Senate. His plans promptly collide with political corruption, but he doesn't back down.</description>
		<price>7</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>122</id>
		<image>img/tt0047296.jpg</image>
		<score>8.3</score>
		<genre>Crime</genre>
		<title>On the Waterfront</title>
		<year>1954</year>
		<description>An ex-prize fighter turned longshoreman struggles to stand up to his corrupt union bosses.</description>
		<price>1</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>123</id>
		<image>img/tt0113277.jpg</image>
		<score>8.3</score>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<title>Heat</title>
		<year>1995</year>
		<description>A group of professional bank robbers start to feel the heat from police when they unknowingly leave a clue at their latest heist.</description>
		<price>2</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>124</id>
		<image>img/tt0050212.jpg</image>
		<score>8.3</score>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<title>The Bridge on the River Kwai</title>
		<year>1957</year>
		<description>After settling his differences with a Japanese PoW camp commander, a British colonel co-operates to oversee his men's construction of a railway bridge for their captors - while oblivious to a plan by the Allies to destroy it.</description>
		<price>3</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>125</id>
		<image>img/tt2106476.jpg</image>
		<score>8.3</score>
		<genre>Drama</genre>
		<title>The Hunt</title>
		<year>2012</year>
		<description>A teacher lives a lonely life, all the while struggling over his son's custody. His life slowly gets better as he finds love and receives good news from his son, but his new luck is about to be brutally shattered by an innocent little lie.</description>
		<price>8</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>126</id>
		<image>img/tt1187043.jpg</image>
		<score>8.5</score>
		<genre>Comedy</genre>
		<title>3 Idiots</title>
		<year>2009</year>
		<description>Two friends are searching for their long lost companion. They revisit their college days and recall the memories of their friend who inspired them to think differently, even as the rest of the world called them &quot;idiots&quot;.</description>
		<price>1</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>127</id>
		<image>img/tt0993846.jpg</image>
		<score>8.3</score>
		<genre>Biography</genre>
		<title>The Wolf of Wall Street</title>
		<year>2013</year>
		<description>Based on the true story of Jordan Belfort, from his rise to a wealthy stock-broker living the high life to his fall involving crime, corruption and the federal government.</description>
		<price>4</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>128</id>
		<image>img/tt0119217.jpg</image>
		<score>8.2</score>
		<genre>Drama</genre>
		<title>Good Will Hunting</title>
		<year>1997</year>
		<description>Will Hunting, a janitor at M.I.T., has a gift for mathematics, but needs help from a psychologist to find direction in his life.</description>
		<price>6</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>129</id>
		<image>img/tt0050976.jpg</image>
		<score>8.3</score>
		<genre>Drama</genre>
		<title>The Seventh Seal</title>
		<year>1957</year>
		<description>A man seeks answers about life, death, and the existence of God as he plays chess against the Grim Reaper during the Black Plague.</description>
		<price>3</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>130</id>
		<image>img/tt0096283.jpg</image>
		<score>8.3</score>
		<genre>Animation</genre>
		<title>My Neighbor Totoro</title>
		<year>1988</year>
		<description>When two girls move to the country to be near their ailing mother, they have adventures with the wonderous forest spirits who live nearby.</description>
		<price>1</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>131</id>
		<image>img/tt0080678.jpg</image>
		<score>8.2</score>
		<genre>Biography</genre>
		<title>The Elephant Man</title>
		<year>1980</year>
		<description>A Victorian surgeon rescues a heavily disfigured man who is mistreated while scraping a living as a side-show freak. Behind his monstrous facade, there is revealed a person of intelligence and sensitivity.</description>
		<price>3</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>132</id>
		<image>img/tt0050986.jpg</image>
		<score>8.3</score>
		<genre>Drama</genre>
		<title>Wild Strawberries</title>
		<year>1957</year>
		<description>After living a life marked by coldness, an aging professor is forced to confront the emptiness of his existence.</description>
		<price>6</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>133</id>
		<image>img/tt0015864.jpg</image>
		<score>8.3</score>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<title>The Gold Rush</title>
		<year>1925</year>
		<description>The Tramp goes to the Klondike in search of gold and finds it and more.</description>
		<price>7</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>134</id>
		<image>img/tt0089881.jpg</image>
		<score>8.3</score>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<title>Ran</title>
		<year>1985</year>
		<description>An elderly lord abdicates to his three sons, and the two corrupt ones turn against him.</description>
		<price>1</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>135</id>
		<image>img/tt0083658.jpg</image>
		<score>8.2</score>
		<genre>Sci-Fi</genre>
		<title>Blade Runner</title>
		<year>1982</year>
		<description>A blade runner must pursue and try to terminate four replicants who stole a ship in space and have returned to Earth to find their creator.</description>
		<price>2</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>136</id>
		<image>img/tt0017925.jpg</image>
		<score>8.3</score>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<title>The General</title>
		<year>1926</year>
		<description>When Union spies steal an engineer's beloved locomotive, he pursues it single handedly and straight through enemy lines.</description>
		<price>2</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>137</id>
		<image>img/tt0120735.jpg</image>
		<score>8.2</score>
		<genre>Comedy</genre>
		<title>Lock, Stock and Two Smoking Barrels</title>
		<year>1998</year>
		<description>A botched card game in London triggers four friends, thugs, weed-growers, hard gangsters, loan sharks and debt collectors to collide with each other in a series of unexpected events, all for the sake of weed, cash and two antique shotguns.</description>
		<price>2</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>138</id>
		<image>img/tt0044741.jpg</image>
		<score>8.4</score>
		<genre>Drama</genre>
		<title>Ikiru</title>
		<year>1952</year>
		<description>A bureaucrat tries to find a meaning in his life after he discovers he has terminal cancer.</description>
		<price>5</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>139</id>
		<image>img/tt1205489.jpg</image>
		<score>8.2</score>
		<genre>Drama</genre>
		<title>Gran Torino</title>
		<year>2008</year>
		<description>Disgruntled Korean War veteran Walt Kowalski sets out to reform his neighbor, a Hmong teenager who tried to steal Kowalski's prized possession: a 1972 Gran Torino.</description>
		<price>7</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>140</id>
		<image>img/tt1305806.jpg</image>
		<score>8.3</score>
		<genre>Drama</genre>
		<title>The Secret in Their Eyes</title>
		<year>2009</year>
		<description>A retired legal counselor writes a novel hoping to find closure for one of his past unresolved homicide cases and for his unreciprocated love with his superior - both of which still haunt him decades later.</description>
		<price>2</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>141</id>
		<image>img/tt0112641.jpg</image>
		<score>8.2</score>
		<genre>Biography</genre>
		<title>Casino</title>
		<year>1995</year>
		<description>Greed, deception, money, power, and murder occur between two mobster best friends and a trophy wife over a gambling empire.</description>
		<price>3</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>142</id>
		<image>img/tt0118715.jpg</image>
		<score>8.2</score>
		<genre>Comedy</genre>
		<title>The Big Lebowski</title>
		<year>1998</year>
		<description>&quot;The Dude&quot; Lebowski, mistaken for a millionaire Lebowski, seeks restitution for his ruined rug and enlists his bowling buddies to help get it.</description>
		<price>8</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>143</id>
		<image>img/tt1291584.jpg</image>
		<score>8.2</score>
		<genre>Drama</genre>
		<title>Warrior</title>
		<year>2011</year>
		<description>The youngest son of an alcoholic former boxer returns home, where he's trained by his father for competition in a mixed martial arts tournament - a path that puts the fighter on a collision corner with his older brother.</description>
		<price>8</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>144</id>
		<image>img/tt0032976.jpg</image>
		<score>8.2</score>
		<genre>Mystery</genre>
		<title>Rebecca</title>
		<year>1940</year>
		<description>A self-conscious bride is tormented by the memory of her husband's dead first wife.</description>
		<price>0</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>145</id>
		<image>img/tt0434409.jpg</image>
		<score>8.2</score>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<title>V for Vendetta</title>
		<year>2005</year>
		<description>In a future British tyranny, a shadowy freedom fighter plots to overthrow it with the help of a young woman.</description>
		<price>3</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>146</id>
		<image>img/tt0025316.jpg</image>
		<score>8.3</score>
		<genre>Comedy</genre>
		<title>It Happened One Night</title>
		<year>1934</year>
		<description>A spoiled heiress, running away from her family, is helped by a man who's actually a reporter looking for a story.</description>
		<price>4</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>147</id>
		<image>img/tt0077416.jpg</image>
		<score>8.2</score>
		<genre>Drama</genre>
		<title>The Deer Hunter</title>
		<year>1978</year>
		<description>An in-depth examination of the ways in which the U.S. Vietnam war impacts and disrupts the lives of people in a small industrial town in Pennsylvania.</description>
		<price>6</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>148</id>
		<image>img/tt0347149.jpg</image>
		<score>8.2</score>
		<genre>Animation</genre>
		<title>Howl's Moving Castle</title>
		<year>2004</year>
		<description>When an unconfident young woman is cursed with an old body by a spiteful witch, her only chance of breaking the spell lies with a self-indulgent yet insecure young wizard and his companions in his legged, walking home.</description>
		<price>4</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>149</id>
		<image>img/tt0061512.jpg</image>
		<score>8.2</score>
		<genre>Crime</genre>
		<title>Cool Hand Luke</title>
		<year>1967</year>
		<description>A man refuses to conform to life in a rural prison.</description>
		<price>4</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>150</id>
		<image>img/tt1979320.jpg</image>
		<score>8.2</score>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<title>Rush</title>
		<year>2013</year>
		<description>The merciless 1970s rivalry between Formula One rivals James Hunt and Niki Lauda.</description>
		<price>5</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>151</id>
		<image>img/tt0892769.jpg</image>
		<score>8.2</score>
		<genre>Animation</genre>
		<title>How to Train Your Dragon</title>
		<year>2010</year>
		<description>A hapless young Viking who aspires to hunt dragons becomes the unlikely friend of a young dragon himself, and learns there may be more to the creatures than he assumed.</description>
		<price>7</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>152</id>
		<image>img/tt0116282.jpg</image>
		<score>8.2</score>
		<genre>Crime</genre>
		<title>Fargo</title>
		<year>1996</year>
		<description>Jerry Lundegaard's inept crime falls apart due to his and his henchmen's bungling and the persistent police work of the quite pregnant Marge Gunderson.</description>
		<price>6</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>153</id>
		<image>img/tt0292490.jpg</image>
		<score>8.5</score>
		<genre>Comedy</genre>
		<title>Dil Chahta Hai</title>
		<year>2001</year>
		<description>Three individual's relationships and the effect that these relationships have on them.</description>
		<price>3</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>154</id>
		<image>img/tt0031381.jpg</image>
		<score>8.2</score>
		<genre>Drama</genre>
		<title>Gone with the Wind</title>
		<year>1939</year>
		<description>A manipulative Southern belle carries on a turbulent affair with a blockade runner during the American Civil War.</description>
		<price>7</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>155</id>
		<image>img/tt0117951.jpg</image>
		<score>8.2</score>
		<genre>Drama</genre>
		<title>Trainspotting</title>
		<year>1996</year>
		<description>Renton, deeply immersed in the Edinburgh drug scene, tries to clean up and get out, despite the allure of the drugs and influence of friends.</description>
		<price>1</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>156</id>
		<image>img/tt0033870.jpg</image>
		<score>8.2</score>
		<genre>Drama</genre>
		<title>The Maltese Falcon</title>
		<year>1941</year>
		<description>A private detective takes on a case that involves him with three eccentric criminals, a gorgeous liar, and their quest for a priceless statuette.</description>
		<price>5</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>157</id>
		<image>img/tt0758758.jpg</image>
		<score>8.2</score>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<title>Into the Wild</title>
		<year>2007</year>
		<description>After graduating from Emory University, top student and athlete Christopher McCandless abandons his possessions, gives his entire $24,000 savings account to charity and hitchhikes to Alaska to live in the wilderness. Along the way, Christopher encounters a series of characters that shape his life.</description>
		<price>7</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>158</id>
		<image>img/tt0055031.jpg</image>
		<score>8.3</score>
		<genre>Drama</genre>
		<title>Judgment at Nuremberg</title>
		<year>1961</year>
		<description>In 1948, an American court in occupied Germany tries four Nazi judges for war crimes.</description>
		<price>2</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>159</id>
		<image>img/tt0405508.jpg</image>
		<score>8.5</score>
		<genre>Drama</genre>
		<title>Colour It Yellow</title>
		<year>2006</year>
		<description>A young woman from England comes to India to make a documentary about her grandfather's diary which was written in the 1920s about the Indian Independence with five young men.</description>
		<price>3</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>160</id>
		<image>img/tt0268978.jpg</image>
		<score>8.2</score>
		<genre>Biography</genre>
		<title>A Beautiful Mind</title>
		<year>2001</year>
		<description>After a brilliant but asocial mathematician accepts secret work in cryptography, his life takes a turn for the nightmarish.</description>
		<price>1</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>161</id>
		<image>img/tt0395169.jpg</image>
		<score>8.2</score>
		<genre>Drama</genre>
		<title>Hotel Rwanda</title>
		<year>2004</year>
		<description>The true story of Paul Rusesabagina, a hotel manager who housed over a thousand Tutsi refugees during their struggle against the Hutu militia in Rwanda.</description>
		<price>4</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>162</id>
		<image>img/tt0167404.jpg</image>
		<score>8.2</score>
		<genre>Drama</genre>
		<title>The Sixth Sense</title>
		<year>1999</year>
		<description>A boy who communicates with spirits that don't know they're dead seeks the help of a disheartened child psychologist.</description>
		<price>5</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>163</id>
		<image>img/tt0046912.jpg</image>
		<score>8.2</score>
		<genre>Crime</genre>
		<title>Dial M for Murder</title>
		<year>1954</year>
		<description>An ex-tennis pro carries out a plot to murder his wife. When things go wrong, he improvises a brilliant plan B.</description>
		<price>3</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>164</id>
		<image>img/tt0084787.jpg</image>
		<score>8.2</score>
		<genre>Horror</genre>
		<title>The Thing</title>
		<year>1982</year>
		<description>Scientists in the Antarctic are confronted by a shape-shifting alien that assumes the appearance of the people that it kills.</description>
		<price>5</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>165</id>
		<image>img/tt2024544.jpg</image>
		<score>8.2</score>
		<genre>Biography</genre>
		<title>12 Years a Slave</title>
		<year>2013</year>
		<description>In the antebellum United States, Solomon Northup, a free black man from upstate New York, is abducted and sold into slavery.</description>
		<price>8</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>166</id>
		<image>img/tt0064115.jpg</image>
		<score>8.2</score>
		<genre>Biography</genre>
		<title>Butch Cassidy and the Sundance Kid</title>
		<year>1969</year>
		<description>Two Western bank/train robbers flee to Bolivia when the law gets too close.</description>
		<price>5</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>167</id>
		<image>img/tt1877832.jpg</image>
		<score>8.2</score>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<title>X-Men: Days of Future Past</title>
		<year>2014</year>
		<description>The X-Men send Wolverine to the past in a desperate effort to change history and prevent an event that results in doom for both humans and mutants.</description>
		<price>1</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>168</id>
		<image>img/tt0266543.jpg</image>
		<score>8.2</score>
		<genre>Animation</genre>
		<title>Finding Nemo</title>
		<year>2003</year>
		<description>After his son is captured in the Great Barrier Reef and taken to Sydney, a timid clownfish sets out on a journey to bring him home.</description>
		<price>3</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>169</id>
		<image>img/tt0477348.jpg</image>
		<score>8.2</score>
		<genre>Crime</genre>
		<title>No Country for Old Men</title>
		<year>2007</year>
		<description>Violence and mayhem ensue after a hunter stumbles upon a drug deal gone wrong and more than two million dollars in cash near the Rio Grande.</description>
		<price>4</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>170</id>
		<image>img/tt0046268.jpg</image>
		<score>8.3</score>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<title>The Wages of Fear</title>
		<year>1953</year>
		<description>In a decrepit South American village, men are hired to transport an urgent nitroglycerine shipment without the equipment that would make it safe.</description>
		<price>4</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>171</id>
		<image>img/tt0266697.jpg</image>
		<score>8.2</score>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<title>Kill Bill: Vol. 1</title>
		<year>2003</year>
		<description>The Bride wakens from a four-year coma. The child she carried in her womb is gone. Now she must wreak vengeance on the team of assassins who betrayed her - a team she was once part of.</description>
		<price>1</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>172</id>
		<image>img/tt0091763.jpg</image>
		<score>8.2</score>
		<genre>Drama</genre>
		<title>Platoon</title>
		<year>1986</year>
		<description>A young recruit in Vietnam faces a moral crisis when confronted with the horrors of war and the duality of man.</description>
		<price>1</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>173</id>
		<image>img/tt0978762.jpg</image>
		<score>8.2</score>
		<genre>Animation</genre>
		<title>Mary and Max</title>
		<year>2009</year>
		<description>A tale of friendship between two unlikely pen pals: Mary, a lonely, eight-year-old girl living in the suburbs of Melbourne, and Max, a forty-four-year old, severely obese man living in New York.</description>
		<price>7</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>174</id>
		<image>img/tt0079470.jpg</image>
		<score>8.2</score>
		<genre>Comedy</genre>
		<title>Life of Brian</title>
		<year>1979</year>
		<description>Brian is born on the original Christmas, in the stable next door. He spends his life being mistaken for a messiah.</description>
		<price>3</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>175</id>
		<image>img/tt0401792.jpg</image>
		<score>8.2</score>
		<genre>Crime</genre>
		<title>Sin City</title>
		<year>2005</year>
		<description>A film that explores the dark and miserable town, Basin City, and tells the story of three different people, all caught up in violent corruption.</description>
		<price>0</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>176</id>
		<image>img/tt0075686.jpg</image>
		<score>8.2</score>
		<genre>Comedy</genre>
		<title>Annie Hall</title>
		<year>1977</year>
		<description>Neurotic New York comedian Alvy Singer falls in love with the ditsy Annie Hall.</description>
		<price>5</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>177</id>
		<image>img/tt0074958.jpg</image>
		<score>8.2</score>
		<genre>Drama</genre>
		<title>Network</title>
		<year>1976</year>
		<description>A television network cynically exploits a deranged former anchor's ravings and revelations about the news media for its own profit.</description>
		<price>8</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>178</id>
		<image>img/tt0052311.jpg</image>
		<score>8.2</score>
		<genre>Crime</genre>
		<title>Touch of Evil</title>
		<year>1958</year>
		<description>A stark, perverse story of murder, kidnapping, and police corruption in a Mexican border town.</description>
		<price>8</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>179</id>
		<image>img/tt2278388.jpg</image>
		<score>8.2</score>
		<genre>Comedy</genre>
		<title>The Grand Budapest Hotel</title>
		<year>2014</year>
		<description>The adventures of Gustave H, a legendary concierge at a famous hotel from the fictional Republic of Zubrowka between the first and second World Wars, and Zero Moustafa, the lobby boy who becomes his most trusted friend.</description>
		<price>4</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>180</id>
		<image>img/tt1255953.jpg</image>
		<score>8.2</score>
		<genre>Drama</genre>
		<title>Incendies</title>
		<year>2010</year>
		<description>Twins journey to the Middle East to discover their family history, and fulfill their mother's last wishes.</description>
		<price>4</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>181</id>
		<image>img/tt0046911.jpg</image>
		<score>8.2</score>
		<genre>Horror</genre>
		<title>Diabolique</title>
		<year>1955</year>
		<description>The wife of a cruel headmaster and his mistress conspire to kill him, but after the murder is committed, his body disappears, and strange events begin to plague the two women.</description>
		<price>8</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>182</id>
		<image>img/tt0092005.jpg</image>
		<score>8.1</score>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<title>Stand by Me</title>
		<year>1986</year>
		<description>After the death of a friend, a writer recounts a boyhood journey to find the body of a missing boy.</description>
		<price>5</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>183</id>
		<image>img/tt0093779.jpg</image>
		<score>8.2</score>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<title>The Princess Bride</title>
		<year>1987</year>
		<description>A classic fairy tale, with swordplay, giants, an evil prince, a beautiful princess, and yes, some kissing (as read by a kindly grandfather).</description>
		<price>5</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>184</id>
		<image>img/tt0469494.jpg</image>
		<score>8.1</score>
		<genre>Drama</genre>
		<title>There Will Be Blood</title>
		<year>2007</year>
		<description>A story of family, religion, hatred, oil and madness, focusing on a turn-of-the-century prospector in the early days of the business.</description>
		<price>2</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>185</id>
		<image>img/tt0052618.jpg</image>
		<score>8.1</score>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<title>Ben-Hur</title>
		<year>1959</year>
		<description>When a Jewish prince is betrayed and sent into slavery by a Roman friend, he regains his freedom and comes back for revenge.</description>
		<price>6</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>186</id>
		<image>img/tt0245712.jpg</image>
		<score>8.1</score>
		<genre>Drama</genre>
		<title>Amores Perros</title>
		<year>2000</year>
		<description>A horrific car accident connects three stories, each involving characters dealing with loss, regret, and life's harsh realities, all in the name of love.</description>
		<price>4</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>187</id>
		<image>img/tt0032138.jpg</image>
		<score>8.1</score>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<title>The Wizard of Oz</title>
		<year>1939</year>
		<description>Dorothy Gale is swept away to a magical land in a tornado and embarks on a quest to see the Wizard who can help her return home.</description>
		<price>4</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>188</id>
		<image>img/tt0405159.jpg</image>
		<score>8.1</score>
		<genre>Drama</genre>
		<title>Million Dollar Baby</title>
		<year>2004</year>
		<description>A determined woman works with a hardened boxing trainer to become a professional.</description>
		<price>1</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>189</id>
		<image>img/tt0848228.jpg</image>
		<score>8.2</score>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<title>The Avengers</title>
		<year>2012</year>
		<description>Earth's mightiest heroes must come together and learn to fight as a team if they are to stop the mischievous Loki and his alien army from enslaving humanity.</description>
		<price>6</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>190</id>
		<image>img/tt0053198.jpg</image>
		<score>8.2</score>
		<genre>Crime</genre>
		<title>The 400 Blows</title>
		<year>1959</year>
		<description>Intensely touching story of a misunderstood young adolescent who left without attention, delves into a life of petty crime.</description>
		<price>8</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>191</id>
		<image>img/tt0032551.jpg</image>
		<score>8.2</score>
		<genre>Drama</genre>
		<title>The Grapes of Wrath</title>
		<year>1940</year>
		<description>A poor Midwest family is forced off of their land. They travel to California, suffering the misfortunes of the homeless in the Great Depression.</description>
		<price>3</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>192</id>
		<image>img/tt1028532.jpg</image>
		<score>8.2</score>
		<genre>Drama</genre>
		<title>Hachi: A Dog's Tale</title>
		<year>2009</year>
		<description>A drama based on the true story of a college professor's bond with the abandoned dog he takes into his home.</description>
		<price>8</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>193</id>
		<image>img/tt0107207.jpg</image>
		<score>8.1</score>
		<genre>Biography</genre>
		<title>In the Name of the Father</title>
		<year>1993</year>
		<description>A man's coerced confession to an IRA bombing he did not commit results in the imprisonment of his father as well. An English lawyer fights to free them.</description>
		<price>5</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>194</id>
		<image>img/tt0036868.jpg</image>
		<score>8.2</score>
		<genre>Drama</genre>
		<title>The Best Years of Our Lives</title>
		<year>1946</year>
		<description>Three WWII veterans return home to small-town America to discover that they and their families have been irreparably changed.</description>
		<price>7</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>195</id>
		<image>img/tt0440963.jpg</image>
		<score>8.1</score>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<title>The Bourne Ultimatum</title>
		<year>2007</year>
		<description>Jason Bourne dodges a ruthless CIA official and his agents from a new assassination program while searching for the origins of his life as a trained killer.</description>
		<price>2</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>196</id>
		<image>img/tt0060827.jpg</image>
		<score>8.2</score>
		<genre>Drama</genre>
		<title>Persona</title>
		<year>1966</year>
		<description>A nurse is put in charge of an actress who can't talk and finds that the actress's persona is melding with hers.</description>
		<price>3</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>197</id>
		<image>img/tt0246578.jpg</image>
		<score>8.1</score>
		<genre>Drama</genre>
		<title>Donnie Darko</title>
		<year>2001</year>
		<description>A troubled teenager is plagued by visions of a large bunny rabbit that manipulates him to commit a series of crimes, after narrowly escaping a bizarre accident.</description>
		<price>3</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>198</id>
		<image>img/tt0083987.jpg</image>
		<score>8.1</score>
		<genre>Biography</genre>
		<title>Gandhi</title>
		<year>1982</year>
		<description>Biography of Mohandas K. Gandhi, the lawyer who became the famed leader of the Indian revolts against the British rule through his philosophy of nonviolent protest.</description>
		<price>2</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>199</id>
		<image>img/tt0044079.jpg</image>
		<score>8.1</score>
		<genre>Crime</genre>
		<title>Strangers on a Train</title>
		<year>1951</year>
		<description>A psychotic socialite confronts a pro tennis star with a theory on how two complete strangers can get away with murder...a theory that he plans to implement.</description>
		<price>0</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>200</id>
		<image>img/tt0056801.jpg</image>
		<score>8.2</score>
		<genre>Drama</genre>
		<title>8½</title>
		<year>1963</year>
		<description>A harried movie director retreats into his memories and fantasies.</description>
		<price>8</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>201</id>
		<image>img/tt0087544.jpg</image>
		<score>8.2</score>
		<genre>Animation</genre>
		<title>Nausicaä of the Valley of the Wind</title>
		<year>1984</year>
		<description>Warrior/pacifist Princess Nausicaä desperately struggles to prevent two warring nations from destroying themselves and their dying planet.</description>
		<price>6</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>202</id>
		<image>img/tt0073195.jpg</image>
		<score>8.1</score>
		<genre>Drama</genre>
		<title>Jaws</title>
		<year>1975</year>
		<description>When a gigantic great white shark begins to menace the small island community of Amity, a police chief, a marine scientist and grizzled fisherman set out to stop it.</description>
		<price>5</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>203</id>
		<image>img/tt0338564.jpg</image>
		<score>8.1</score>
		<genre>Crime</genre>
		<title>Infernal Affairs</title>
		<year>2002</year>
		<description>A story between a mole in the police department and an undercover cop. Their objectives are the same: to find out who is the mole, and who is the cop.</description>
		<price>8</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>204</id>
		<image>img/tt0044706.jpg</image>
		<score>8.1</score>
		<genre>Drama</genre>
		<title>High Noon</title>
		<year>1952</year>
		<description>A marshall, personally compelled to face a returning deadly enemy, finds that his own town refuses to help him.</description>
		<price>6</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>205</id>
		<image>img/tt0114746.jpg</image>
		<score>8.1</score>
		<genre>Mystery</genre>
		<title>Twelve Monkeys</title>
		<year>1995</year>
		<description>In a future world devastated by disease, a convict is sent back in time to gather information about the man-made virus that wiped out most of the human population on the planet.</description>
		<price>6</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>206</id>
		<image>img/tt1504320.jpg</image>
		<score>8.1</score>
		<genre>Biography</genre>
		<title>The King's Speech</title>
		<year>2010</year>
		<description>The story of King George VI of the United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland, his impromptu ascension to the throne and the speech therapist who helped the unsure monarch become worthy of it.</description>
		<price>8</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>207</id>
		<image>img/tt0038787.jpg</image>
		<score>8.1</score>
		<genre>Drama</genre>
		<title>Notorious</title>
		<year>1946</year>
		<description>A woman is asked to spy on a group of Nazi friends in South America. How far will she have to go to ingratiate herself with them?</description>
		<price>1</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>208</id>
		<image>img/tt0088247.jpg</image>
		<score>8.1</score>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<title>The Terminator</title>
		<year>1984</year>
		<description>A human-looking indestructible cyborg is sent from 2029 to 1984 to assassinate a waitress, whose unborn son will lead humanity in a war against the machines, while a soldier from that war is sent to protect her at all costs.</description>
		<price>7</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>209</id>
		<image>img/tt1130884.jpg</image>
		<score>8.1</score>
		<genre>Mystery</genre>
		<title>Shutter Island</title>
		<year>2010</year>
		<description>In 1954, U.S. Marshal Teddy Daniels is investigating the disappearance of a murderess who escaped from a hospital for the criminally insane and is presumed to be hiding near-by.</description>
		<price>3</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>210</id>
		<image>img/tt0079944.jpg</image>
		<score>8.2</score>
		<genre>Drama</genre>
		<title>Stalker</title>
		<year>1979</year>
		<description>A guide leads two men through an area known as the Zone to find a room that grants wishes.</description>
		<price>3</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>211</id>
		<image>img/tt1201607.jpg</image>
		<score>8.1</score>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<title>Harry Potter and the Deathly Hallows: Part 2</title>
		<year>2011</year>
		<description>Harry, Ron and Hermione search for Voldemort's remaining Horcruxes in their effort to destroy the Dark Lord as the final battle rages on at Hogwarts.</description>
		<price>7</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>212</id>
		<image>img/tt0107048.jpg</image>
		<score>8.1</score>
		<genre>Comedy</genre>
		<title>Groundhog Day</title>
		<year>1993</year>
		<description>A weatherman finds himself living the same day over and over again.</description>
		<price>2</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>213</id>
		<image>img/tt1220719.jpg</image>
		<score>8.1</score>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<title>Ip Man</title>
		<year>2008</year>
		<description>A semi-biographical account of Yip Man, the first martial arts master to teach the Chinese martial art of Wing Chun.</description>
		<price>5</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>214</id>
		<image>img/tt0083922.jpg</image>
		<score>8.2</score>
		<genre>Drama</genre>
		<title>Fanny and Alexander</title>
		<year>1982</year>
		<description>Two young Swedish children experience the many comedies and tragedies of their family, the Ekdahls.</description>
		<price>1</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>215</id>
		<image>img/tt0075148.jpg</image>
		<score>8.1</score>
		<genre>Drama</genre>
		<title>Rocky</title>
		<year>1976</year>
		<description>Rocky Balboa, a small-time boxer gets a supremely rare chance to fight the heavy-weight champion, Apollo Creed, in a bout in which he strives to go the distance for his self-respect.</description>
		<price>6</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>216</id>
		<image>img/tt0112471.jpg</image>
		<score>8.1</score>
		<genre>Drama</genre>
		<title>Before Sunrise</title>
		<year>1995</year>
		<description>A young man and woman meet on a train in Europe, and wind up spending one evening together in Vienna. Unfortunately, both know that this will probably be their only night together.</description>
		<price>4</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>217</id>
		<image>img/tt0048424.jpg</image>
		<score>8.1</score>
		<genre>Crime</genre>
		<title>The Night of the Hunter</title>
		<year>1955</year>
		<description>A religious fanatic marries a gullible widow whose young children are reluctant to tell him where their real daddy hid $10,000 he'd stolen in a robbery.</description>
		<price>4</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>218</id>
		<image>img/tt0072890.jpg</image>
		<score>8.1</score>
		<genre>Crime</genre>
		<title>Dog Day Afternoon</title>
		<year>1975</year>
		<description>A man robs a bank to pay for his lover's operation; it turns into a hostage situation and a media circus.</description>
		<price>6</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>219</id>
		<image>img/tt0169102.jpg</image>
		<score>8.3</score>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<title>Lagaan: Once Upon a Time in India</title>
		<year>2001</year>
		<description>The people of a small village in Victorian India stake their future on a game of cricket against their ruthless British rulers...</description>
		<price>4</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>220</id>
		<image>img/tt0198781.jpg</image>
		<score>8.1</score>
		<genre>Animation</genre>
		<title>Monsters, Inc.</title>
		<year>2001</year>
		<description>Monsters generate their city's power by scaring children, but they are terribly afraid themselves of being contaminated by children, so when one enters Monstropolis, top scarer Sulley finds his world disrupted.</description>
		<price>0</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>221</id>
		<image>img/tt0113247.jpg</image>
		<score>8.1</score>
		<genre>Drama</genre>
		<title>La Haine</title>
		<year>1995</year>
		<description>After local youth Abdel is beaten unconscious by police, a riot ensues on his estate during which a policeman loses his gun. The gun is found by Vinz who threatens he will kill a cop if Abdel dies.</description>
		<price>6</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>222</id>
		<image>img/tt0047528.jpg</image>
		<score>8.1</score>
		<genre>Drama</genre>
		<title>La Strada</title>
		<year>1954</year>
		<description>A care-free girl is sold to a traveling entertainer, consequently enduring physical and emotional pain along the way.</description>
		<price>4</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>223</id>
		<image>img/tt0325980.jpg</image>
		<score>8.1</score>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<title>Pirates of the Caribbean: The Curse of the Black Pearl</title>
		<year>2003</year>
		<description>Blacksmith Will Turner teams up with eccentric pirate &quot;Captain&quot; Jack Sparrow to save his love, the governor's daughter, from Jack's former pirate allies, who are now undead.</description>
		<price>5</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>224</id>
		<image>img/tt0058946.jpg</image>
		<score>8.2</score>
		<genre>Crime</genre>
		<title>The Battle of Algiers</title>
		<year>1966</year>
		<description>In the 1950s, fear and violence escalate as the people of Algiers fight for independence from the French government.</description>
		<price>4</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>225</id>
		<image>img/tt0072684.jpg</image>
		<score>8.1</score>
		<genre>Drama</genre>
		<title>Barry Lyndon</title>
		<year>1975</year>
		<description>An Irish rogue wins the heart of a rich widow and assumes her dead husband's aristocratic position in 18th-century England.</description>
		<price>2</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>226</id>
		<image>img/tt0061184.jpg</image>
		<score>8.1</score>
		<genre>Drama</genre>
		<title>Who's Afraid of Virginia Woolf?</title>
		<year>1966</year>
		<description>A bitter aging couple with the help of alcohol, use a young couple to fuel anguish and emotional pain towards each other.</description>
		<price>4</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>227</id>
		<image>img/tt0353969.jpg</image>
		<score>8.1</score>
		<genre>Crime</genre>
		<title>Memories of Murder</title>
		<year>2003</year>
		<description>In 1986, in the province of Gyunggi, in South Korea, a second young and beautiful woman is found dead...</description>
		<price>4</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>228</id>
		<image>img/tt0058461.jpg</image>
		<score>8.1</score>
		<genre>Western</genre>
		<title>A Fistful of Dollars</title>
		<year>1964</year>
		<description>A wandering gunfighter plays two rival families against each other in a town torn apart by greed, pride, and revenge.</description>
		<price>1</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>229</id>
		<image>img/tt0038355.jpg</image>
		<score>8.1</score>
		<genre>Crime</genre>
		<title>The Big Sleep</title>
		<year>1946</year>
		<description>Private detective Philip Marlowe is hired by a rich family. Before the complex case is over, he's seen murder, blackmail, and what might be love.</description>
		<price>5</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>230</id>
		<image>img/tt1798709.jpg</image>
		<score>8.1</score>
		<genre>Drama</genre>
		<title>Her</title>
		<year>2013</year>
		<description>A lonely writer develops an unlikely relationship with his newly purchased operating system that's designed to meet his every need.</description>
		<price>5</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>231</id>
		<image>img/tt0092067.jpg</image>
		<score>8.1</score>
		<genre>Animation</genre>
		<title>Castle in the Sky</title>
		<year>1986</year>
		<description>A young boy and a girl with a magic crystal must race against pirates and foreign agents in a search for a legendary floating castle.</description>
		<price>4</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>232</id>
		<image>img/tt0120382.jpg</image>
		<score>8</score>
		<genre>Comedy</genre>
		<title>The Truman Show</title>
		<year>1998</year>
		<description>An insurance salesman/adjuster discovers his entire life is actually a T.V. show.</description>
		<price>7</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>233</id>
		<image>img/tt0061722.jpg</image>
		<score>8.1</score>
		<genre>Comedy</genre>
		<title>The Graduate</title>
		<year>1967</year>
		<description>Recent college graduate Benjamin Braddock is trapped into an affair with Mrs. Robinson, who happens to be the wife of his father's business partner and then finds himself falling in love with her daughter, Elaine.</description>
		<price>5</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>234</id>
		<image>img/tt1454029.jpg</image>
		<score>8.1</score>
		<genre>Drama</genre>
		<title>The Help</title>
		<year>2011</year>
		<description>An aspiring author during the civil rights movement of the 1960s decides to write a book detailing the African-American maids' point of view on the white families for which they work, and the hardships they go through on a daily basis.</description>
		<price>7</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>235</id>
		<image>img/tt0046250.jpg</image>
		<score>8.1</score>
		<genre>Comedy</genre>
		<title>Roman Holiday</title>
		<year>1953</year>
		<description>A bored and sheltered princess escapes her guardians and falls in love with an American newsman in Rome.</description>
		<price>4</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>236</id>
		<image>img/tt0054997.jpg</image>
		<score>8.1</score>
		<genre>Drama</genre>
		<title>The Hustler</title>
		<year>1961</year>
		<description>An up-and-coming pool player plays a long-time champion in a single high-stakes match.</description>
		<price>7</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>237</id>
		<image>img/tt0107290.jpg</image>
		<score>8</score>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<title>Jurassic Park</title>
		<year>1993</year>
		<description>During a preview tour, a theme park suffers a major power breakdown that allows its cloned dinosaur exhibits to run amok.</description>
		<price>1</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>238</id>
		<image>img/tt0154420.jpg</image>
		<score>8.1</score>
		<genre>Drama</genre>
		<title>The Celebration</title>
		<year>1998</year>
		<description>At Helge's 60th birthday party, some unpleasant family truths are revealed.</description>
		<price>3</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>239</id>
		<image>img/tt0118694.jpg</image>
		<score>8.1</score>
		<genre>Drama</genre>
		<title>In the Mood for Love</title>
		<year>2000</year>
		<description>Two neighbors, a woman and a man, form a strong bond after both suspect extramarital activities of their spouses. However, they agree to keep their bond platonic so as not to commit similar wrongs.</description>
		<price>8</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>240</id>
		<image>img/tt0101414.jpg</image>
		<score>8.1</score>
		<genre>Animation</genre>
		<title>Beauty and the Beast</title>
		<year>1991</year>
		<description>Belle, whose father is imprisoned by the Beast, offers herself instead and discovers her captor to be an enchanted prince.</description>
		<price>8</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>241</id>
		<image>img/tt0046359.jpg</image>
		<score>8.1</score>
		<genre>Comedy</genre>
		<title>Stalag 17</title>
		<year>1953</year>
		<description>When two escaping American World War II prisoners are killed, the German POW camp barracks black marketeer, J.J. Sefton, is suspected of being an informer.</description>
		<price>3</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>242</id>
		<image>img/tt0040746.jpg</image>
		<score>8.1</score>
		<genre>Crime</genre>
		<title>Rope</title>
		<year>1948</year>
		<description>Two young men strangle their &quot;inferior&quot; classmate, hide his body in their apartment, and invite his friends and family to a dinner party as a means to challenge the &quot;perfection&quot; of their crime.</description>
		<price>3</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>243</id>
		<image>img/tt1010048.jpg</image>
		<score>8</score>
		<genre>Drama</genre>
		<title>Slumdog Millionaire</title>
		<year>2008</year>
		<description>A Mumbai teen who grew up in the slums, becomes a contestant on the Indian version of &quot;Who Wants To Be A Millionaire?&quot; He is arrested under suspicion of cheating, and while being interrogated, events from his life history are shown which explain why he knows the answers.</description>
		<price>4</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>244</id>
		<image>img/tt0049406.jpg</image>
		<score>8.1</score>
		<genre>Crime</genre>
		<title>The Killing</title>
		<year>1956</year>
		<description>Crooks plan and execute a daring race-track robbery.</description>
		<price>4</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>245</id>
		<image>img/tt0085334.jpg</image>
		<score>8.1</score>
		<genre>Comedy</genre>
		<title>A Christmas Story</title>
		<year>1983</year>
		<description>Ralphie has to convince his parents, his teacher, and Santa that a Red Ryder B.B. gun really is the perfect gift for the 1940s.</description>
		<price>5</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>246</id>
		<image>img/tt0381681.jpg</image>
		<score>8.1</score>
		<genre>Drama</genre>
		<title>Before Sunset</title>
		<year>2004</year>
		<description>Nine years after Jesse and Celine first met, they encounter each other again on the French leg of Jesse's book tour.</description>
		<price>3</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>247</id>
		<image>img/tt0070511.jpg</image>
		<score>8.1</score>
		<genre>Biography</genre>
		<title>Papillon</title>
		<year>1973</year>
		<description>A man befriends a fellow criminal as the two of them begin serving their sentence on a dreadful prison island, which inspires the man to plot his escape.</description>
		<price>1</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>248</id>
		<image>img/tt0111495.jpg</image>
		<score>8.1</score>
		<genre>Drama</genre>
		<title>Three Colors: Red</title>
		<year>1994</year>
		<description>Final entry in a trilogy of films dealing with contemporary French society concerns a model who discovers her neighbour is keen on invading people's privacy.</description>
		<price>6</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>249</id>
		<image>img/tt0450259.jpg</image>
		<score>8</score>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<title>Blood Diamond</title>
		<year>2006</year>
		<description>A fisherman, a smuggler, and a syndicate of businessmen match wits over the possession of a priceless diamond.</description>
		<price>4</price>
	</movie>
	<movie>
		<id>250</id>
		<image>img/tt0367110.jpg</image>
		<score>8.4</score>
		<genre>Drama</genre>
		<title>Swades</title>
		<year>2004</year>
		<description>A successful Indian scientist returns to an Indian village to take his nanny to America with him and in the process rediscovers his roots.</description>
		<price>8</price>
	</movie>
</catalog>
